Guide to the William Rufus Shafter Papers
Department of Special Collections
- Series VII - Printed Reference
  - Copies (Box 8, Folder 80)
Carter, William H. Lt. Col., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 17 Roll IV Folder 33 Roll V Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 54
Carter, Thomas H. Senator, Montana, 1895 - 1901 Roll VI Folder 53
Cartwright, George S. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Casa Azul Roll III Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 32
Castellonae Sanchez, J. Roll I Folder 10
Castillo, D. Brig. Gen., Cuban Army Roll I Folder 10 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 24, Folder 28 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 57
Castine (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll V Folder 52
Catania (U. S. Ship) Roll IV Folder 38, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43
Cavadonga (Sp. Ship) Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 44
C. B. & O. Railroad Roll VII Folder 50
Cebreco, Juan P. Col., Cuban Army Roll III Folder 25
Censor, U. S. Fellows, Squires Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 43
Century Club of California Roll I Folder 9
The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine Roll VI Folder 45, Folder 53, Folder 65
Cervera, Pascual Admiral, Sp. Naval Squadron Roll II Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 38 Roll V Folder 50 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 57
Cerreoso, Rudolfo Roll IV Folder 36 Roll V Folder 44
Chadwick, F. E. Capt., U. S. N. Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 26, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 30
Chaffee, Adna R. Maj. Gen. Roll II Folder 16, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 54
Champett, Mrs. J. W. Roll VI Folder 53
Champlin, Fred Roll V Folder 45
Chandler, L Roll I Folder 1
Chandler, William A. Capt. Roll III Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Chapin's Farm, Virginia Roll VI Folder 54
Charity, Sisters of Roll IV Folder 42
Charles, Oscar J. Capt. Roll IV Folder 37, Roll V Folder 43
Chase, George F. Capt. Roll IV Folder 39 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 48
Cheever, Benjamin H. Capt. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14
Cherokee (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll VI Folder 52
Chester (U. S. Steamer) Roll V Folder 47
Chicago Herald (Newspaper) Roll I Folder 4
Chicago, Illinois Roll II Folder 17 Roll V Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49
Chicago Peace Jubilee Roll VI Folder 51
Chicago Times (Newspaper) Roll I Folder 4
Chicago Tribune (Newspaper) Roll II Folder 16
Chicago World (Newspaper) Roll I Folder 5
Chicamauga, Georgia Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 27, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30 Roll VI Folder 57
Chihuahua, State of Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 7
Child, Perley A. Roll V Folder 45
Chipman, Jacob Roll VI Folder 53
Chinese Consul Roll III Folder 24
Church, James R. Maj., Asst. Surg. Roll IV Folder 37
Cibrico, [?] Col., Cuban Army Roll III Folder 24
Cienfuegos, Cuba Roll I Folder 9 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 42
Cincinnati, Ohio Roll I Folder 10, Folder 12 Roll VI Folder 51
Circular, Hdq. U. S. Forces, Fifth Army Corps, Camp Santiago de Cuba, July 15 - 24, 1898 Roll II Folder 11
Circular, Hdq. U. S. Forces, Fifth Army Corps, #1, 2, 3 Roll II Folder 11
Circular, Hdq. U. S. Forces, Fifth Army Corps, Montauk Point, Long Island, September 6 - 8, 1898 Roll II Folder 11
Circular, Hdq. U. S. Forces, Fifth Army Corps, Camp Wikoff, Long Island, September 9 - 23, 1898 Roll II Folder 11
Circular, Hdq. U. S. Forces, Tampa, Florida, #1, 2, 3 Roll II Folder 11
City of Mason (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42
City of Washington (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20 Roll IV Folder 31
Civil War Roll II Folder 13 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 55, Folder 56, Folder 57
Clark, [?] Col. Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Clark, Fort (Texas) Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7
Clark, George, L. Lt. Roll I Folder 1
Clark, Robert S. Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42
Clarke, Joseph T. Capt. Roll IV Folder 37
Clay, Evans H. Commissioner of Pensions Roll VI Folder 50
Cleeves, [?] Roll I Folder 3
Clinton, S. S. (U. S. Transport) Roll I Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 36, Folder 43
Clitz, Henry B. Bvt. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 3
Coachman, W. F. Freight Agent Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 14
Coahuila, State of Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 7
Cobre, Cuba Roll III Folder 22, Folder 24, Folder 25 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 43
Coburn, John Col., 1864 Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 30 Roll V Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 57
Cochran, Melville A. Col. Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18
Coe, John N. Maj. Roll I Folder 12
Colbe, Pat Gustane Roll III Folder 22
Colby, A. M. Roll VI Folder 53
Cole, W. R. Roll V Folder 43
Cole, Edwin T. Lt. Roll III Folder 19, Folder 24
Collazo, Enrique Gen., Cuban Forces Roll II Folder 17
Colón (Spanish Ship) Roll III Folder 22, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 39
Colorado, Department of Roll V Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 53
Colored Regiments Roll I Folder 2 Roll II Folder 14, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31
Colored Troops, Organization of (see also Fourteenth, Seventeenth, and Fourty-fourth U. S. Colored Troops Roll I Folder 1 Roll IV Folder 32
Columbia, Department of Roll VI Folder 52 Folder 53, Folder 57
Columbia (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 27, Folder 29
Comal (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 21 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36 Roll VI Folder 52
Comanche (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43
Comba, Richard Col. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 45
Comillas, Marques Roll IV Folder 33
Commission for Articles of Capitulation Roll II Folder 29
Commission to Investigate the Conduct of the War Department in the War with Spain Roll VI Folder 51, Folder 53
Compagnie Française Des Cables Telegraphiques Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44
Concas, [?] Capt., Sp. Navy Roll VI Folder 57
Concho, Fort (Texas) Roll I Folder 1, Folder 6
Concho (U. S. Ship) Roll I Folder 2 Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 20 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 40 Roll VI Folder 52
Condon, William H. Roll VI Folder 50
Conrad, Casper, H. Maj. Roll II Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Cook, Henry F. Roll V Folder 48
Cooke, William N. Roll I Folder 7
Coolidge, Charles A. Maj. Roll III Folder 21, Folder 25 Roll V Folder 46
Copperheads (California) Roll I Folder 1
Coppinger, John J. Maj. Gen. Roll III Folder 25 Roll V Folder 47
Coppini, Pompeo Roll VI Folder 57
Corbin, Henry C. Brig. Gen., A. G. Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 55, Folder 57
Corralillo, Cuba Roll III Folder 28
Court of the First Audiencia Roll V Folder 41
Cox, Mrs. M. Roll V Folder 45
Coxe, Mac Grane Roll V Folder 45
Crabbs, Joseph T. Quartermaster Roll VI Folder 51
Crane, H. M. Roll VI Folder 50
Crawford, John Roll I Folder 2
Crawford, William S. Roll I Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 7
Crowell, [?] Deputy U. S. Marshall Roll I Folder 5
Cuavitas, Cuba Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 34
Cuba, Eastern District of Roll VI Folder 50
Cuba Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 14, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 45, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 54, Folder 57
Cuban Submarine Company Roll III Folder 26
Cumberland, Department of Roll I Folder 1
Cumberland (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 38
Cumfert, Lucy Randall Roll I Folder 8
Custer, [Bethel M.?] [Capt.?] Roll I Folder 5
Cupell, William C. A. A. G., of the State of Massachusetts Roll V Folder 47
Cummins, Albert S. Capt. Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll IV Folder 40
Cunningham, James A. Col. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 6
Custom House, Santiago Roll V Folder 44
Customs, Collector of - Tampa Roll II Folder 12
Cutler, Monte Newsman Roll II Folder 16
Daggett, Aaron S. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35, Folder 37
Dahlgren, [?] Commander Naval Attache Norway and Sweden Roll VI Folder 52
Daiquiri, Cuba Roll I Folder 9 Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28 Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34 Roll V Folder 42 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
Dakota, Department of Roll V Folder 45, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49
Dana, Napoleon J. T. Brig. Gen. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 57
Daniels, William C. Maj. Roll VI Folder 31, Folder 37
Dapray, John A. Lt. Roll I Folder 10
Daugherty, M. J. Roll VI Folder 50
Davis, [?] Asst. to Commissary, Gen. of Subsistance Roll III Folder 26
Davis, Fort (Texas) Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 5
Davis, Richard Harding Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 37 Roll VI Folder 50
Davis William Jr. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 6
Day, Frederick R. Lt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Day, William R. Asst. Sect. of State Roll V Folder 42
Dean Dudly Roll IV Folder 40
Decatur (U. S. Ship) Roll VI Folder 52
Dee (British Steamer) Roll IV Folder 36
Delgado, [?] Insurgent Chief, Cuba Roll I Folder 10
Dention Hospital New York Roll V Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50
Derby, George Mc. Lt. Col. Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 35 Roll V Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 55
Detroit (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
De Vries, Marion Congress, California Roll VI Folder 53
Dewey, George Admiral, U. S. N. Roll IV Folder 35 Roll V Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53
de Young, Meichel H. Roll V Folder 41
D. H. Miller (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44
Diaz, Porfirio Gen., Mex. Army Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5
Dickenson, Don M. Roll I Folder 8
Dillenback, John W. Maj. Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 46
Dillmered, Agnes B. Roll V Folder 45
Dixon, Lulie Roll V Folder 45
Dodge, Francis, S. Maj. Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 47
Dodge, Grenville M. Maj. Gen., President of Commission to Investigate the War Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51
Dodt, Helenus Capt., A. A. G. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7
Dolan, Michael Lt. Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6
Donaldson, James L. Bvt. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 2 Roll VI Folder 58
Donaldson, Walter A. Customs Collector Roll IV Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44
Donovan, Edward Lt. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 6
Dorst, Joseph H. Capt. Roll I Folder 7, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 15 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 36, Folder 37
Dos Caminos del Cobre, Cuba Roll III Folder 24, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36
Downs, W. A. Lt. Col. Roll I Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 48
Dry Tortugas Roll II Folder 12 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 23
Duchess (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 29
Ducrot House, Cuba Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 36
Duffield, Henry M. Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 51
Dumont, John E Roll V Folder 45
Duncan, Fort (Texas) Roll I Folder 2, Folder 3, Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7
Duncan, George B. Lt., A. A. G. Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14
Durton (U. S. Steamer) Roll IV Folder 36
Dysentery Roll III Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 39 Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46
Eagan, Charles P. Roll VI Folder 52
Eagle (U. S. Ship) Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21 Roll VI Folder 52
Earnshaw, William Chaplin Roll I Folder 1
East, Department of the Roll V Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 51, Folder 52, Folder 57
Ebstein, Frederick H. E. Capt. Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Egbert, Harry C. Capt., Col. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 51
Eighth Cavalry Roll V Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 51
Eighth Infantry Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49
Eighth New York Volunteer Infantry Roll V Folder 46
Eighth Ohio Volunteer Infantry Roll III Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 49
Eighth Volunteer Signal Corps Roll V Folder 47
El Caney, Cuba Roll III Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41 Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 57
El Cubano (Cuban Newspaper) Roll VII Folder 77
El Espectador (Cuban Newspaper) Roll VII Folder 77
El Hijo de El Ahuizote (Cuban Newspaper) Roll VII Folder 77
Eleventh Infantry Roll III Folder 19
Ellis, Philip H. Maj. Roll I Folder 5 Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 26
El Parvenir (Cuban Newspaper) Roll VII Folder 77
El Pozo Roll III Folder 24, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31 Roll VI Folder 57
El Pozo, Conference at Roll VI Folder 54
El Pozo House Roll III Folder 23 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 33
Embree, Henry D. Roll VI Folder 52
Encuastic File Works, U. S. Roll V Folder 46
Engineers, Battalion of Roll II Folder 13 Roll III Folder 20, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 52
England Roll II Folder 16
English Cable Company Roll III Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 34
English Expedition to Cuba, 1761 Roll VI Folder 57
English, William Capt. Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 37
Ennis, William Capt. Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 21, Folder 26, Folder 28 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 35, Folder 36 Roll V Folder 42
Enver, Pasha Gen., Turkish Military Attache Roll III Folder 27 Roll VI Folder 52
Ernist, George W. Lt. Roll I Folder 1
Escario, Don Frederick Brig. Gen., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 32, Folder 34, Folder 36
Espana (Sp. Steamer) Roll IV Folder 36
Estrada, Palma Gen., Cuban Forces Roll III Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 32 Roll V Folder 42
Estrella (Sp. Ship) Roll IV Folder 36
Ethan Allen, Fort (Virginia) Roll V Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 48
Evans, George H. Lt. Roll I Folder 2, Folder 4, Folder 7
Evarts, William M. Sect. of State, 1877 - 1881 Roll I Folder 1, Folder 4
Ewers, Ezra P. Brig. Gen. Roll II Folder 12, Folder 16 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44
F. C. & P. Railroad Company, Florida Roll II Folder 14, Folder 16
Fairbanks, Henry N. Roll VI Folder 53
Faircloth, [?] Capt. Roll III Folder 21, Folder 26, Folder 27
Fair Oaks Station, Battle of Roll I Folder 1, Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 54, Folder 57
Falcon, Anacleto R. Gen., Mex. Army Roll I Folder 4, Folder 5, Folder 6, Folder 7
Fanita (Sp. Steamer) Roll III Folder 20
Farnsworth, C. S. Lt. Col. Roll III Folder 23 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37
Farrar, Judson S. Roll IV Folder 36
Favor, Milton Roll I Folder 1
Felix, Flores Roll I Folder 6
Feria, [?] Gen., Cuban Forces Roll III Folder 27
Fern (U. S. Ship) Roll III Folder 27
Fever Hospital Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32
Fields M. Roll I Folder 4
Fifth Artillery Roll III Folder 26, Folder 29 Roll V Folder 43
Fifth Army Corps Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 54, Folder 56, Folder 57
Fifth Cavalry Roll III Folder 19 Roll V Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 49
Fifth Infantry Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 15, Folder 17 Roll V Folder 45, Folder 48
Fifth Michigan Vol. Infantry 1861 - 1864 Roll IV Folder 36
Fifth Ohio Infantry Roll II Folder 14, Folder 16, Folder 17
Fifteenth Infantry Roll V Folder 48
Fifth U. S. Vol. Infantry Roll V Folder 42
Fifty-eight Article of War Roll II Folder 13, Folder 14
Fifty-ninth Article of War Roll II Folder 14
First Artillery Roll II Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52
First Cavalry Roll III Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 37, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52
First District of Columbia Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 37 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 44, Folder 46
First Florida Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19
First Illinois Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 36, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46
First Infantry Roll I Folder 8 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 14, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 23, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52, Folder 54, Folder 57
First Nebraska Vol. Infantry Roll VI Folder 53
First North Carolina Infantry Roll II Folder 15
First Ohio Vol. Infantry Roll II Folder 17 Roll IV Folder 32
First Regular Cavalry Roll V Folder 41
First South Dakota Infantry Roll VI Folder 53
First Texas Cavalry Roll V Folder 44
First U. S. Vol. Cavalry Roll III Folder 16, Folder 19 Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 37, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 52
Fish, Hamilton Jr. Lt. Roll III Folder 20, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 28
Fish, Josiah Capt. Roll I Folder 8
Fisk, Clinton B. Bvt. Maj. Gen. Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 50
Fitzgerald, [?] Roll V Folder 45
Fletcher, [Thomas C.?] Bvt. Gen. of Vols. Roll I Folder 8
Fleves, Antonio Roll I Folder 5
Flint, Eddy & Company Roll IV Folder 36
Florida National Militia Convention Roll VI Folder 52
Florida (U. S. Transport) Roll II Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 23 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31 Roll V Folder 44, Folder 45 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52
Foote, Morris C., Sr. Maj. Roll IV Folder 34, Folder 35
Foraker, Joseph B. Senator of Chio, 1897 - 1903 Roll VI Folder 54
Foraste, Dionisio Sp. Soldier Roll III Folder 27
Forbush, William C, Maj. Roll III Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 31
Forrest, [Nathan B. C.?] Confederate Gen. Roll IV Folder 30 Roll VI Folder 56
Forty-first Infantry Roll I Folder 8 Roll VI Folder 54, Folder 57
Forwood, William H. Col. Roll V Folder 45, Folder 46
Foster, Darin Roll I Folder 7
Foster, George F. Roll V Folder 45
Foster, [John Watson?] Minister to Mex. Roll I Folder 1, Folder 4
Fourteenth U. S. Colored Troops Roll I Folder 1
Fourth Artillery Roll II Folder 13, Folder 16 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50
Fourth Cavalry Roll VI Folder 52
Fourth Infantry Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 14 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 37, Folder 38 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 45, Folder 47 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 52
Fourth Ohio Vol. Roll V Folder 48
Fourth Spanish Corps Roll VI Folder 57
Fox, [E. A.?] A. G. of the State of Washington Roll VI Folder 53
Freeman, Abraham C. Roll IV Folder 31
Freeman, Henry B. Lt. Col. Roll V Folder 45
French Ambassador Roll V Folder 42
French Consul Roll III Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 34, Folder 37
French Expedition to Santiago, 1801 Roll VI Folder 57
Friedander, E. E. Roll I Folder 6
Frontan, Don Ventura Lt. Col., Sp. Forces Roll III Folder 29
Fuller, Dr. Roll IV Folder 40 Roll VI Folder 57
Fuller, George N., PhD., (Ed. MHM) Roll VI Folder 57
Furor (Sp. Torpedo Boat) Roll III Folder 22
Gage, Henry Roll VI Folder 53
Gaillard, David Capt. Roll II Folder 12
Galan, Vicente Roll I Folder 3
Galesburg, Michigan Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
Galesburg Peace Jubilee and State Fair Roll VI Folder 50
Gallagher, Hugh H. Maj. Roll III Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 33, Folder 35, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54
Galloupe, Dwight Chaplin Roll II Folder 14
Garcia, Antonio Roll III Folder 27
García, Calixto Gen., Cuban Forces Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 17, Folder 21, Folder 22, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 36, Folder 37 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43 Roll VI Folder 52, Folder 53, Folder 54, Folder 57
García, Vicente Roll I Folder 23
Garlington, Ernest A. Maj. Roll I Folder 8 Roll IV Folder 31, Folder 36, Folder 37
Garretson, George A. Brig. Gen. Roll III Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 38 Roll VI Folder 54
Garza, Bernado Roll I Folder 5
Garza, Juan Roll I Folder 7
Garza, Vincente Roll I Folder 5, Folder 7
Gate City (U.S. Ship) Roll III Folder 23, Folder 26 Roll IV Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40
General Hospital Roll V Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50
General Order 7 Roll I Folder 2
General Orders, Current Series U. S. Army AGO Roll II Folder 13, Folder 17
General Orders 7, District of the Nueces Roll I Folder 8
General Orders, Fifth Army Roll II Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 20, Folder 25, Folder 27 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46 Roll VI Folder 49, Folder 50
General Orders, U. S. Forces Roll I Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 15
Genova, F. B. Mayor of Saint Augustine, Florida Roll II Folder 17, Folder 18
Geos, Avelino Roll IV Folder 32
Germany Roll II Folder 16
Gettysberg, Battle of Roll I Folder 1
Gibara, Cuba Roll III Folder 22 Roll IV Folder 38
Gilbert, [Rufus H.?] Col. Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 57
Gilmore, John Curtis Brig. Gen. Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 16, Folder 17 Roll III Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 37, Folder 38, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 46
Gilmore, John Curtis, Jr. Roll I Folder 9, Folder 10 Roll II Folder 11, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17, Folder 18 Roll III Folder 19, Folder 21, Folder 23, Folder 24, Folder 25, Folder 26, Folder 27, Folder 28, Folder 29 Roll IV Folder 30, Folder 31, Folder 32, Folder 33, Folder 34, Folder 35, Folder 36, Folder 38, Folder 39, Folder 40 Roll V Folder 41, Folder 42, Folder 43, Folder 44, Folder 45, Folder 46, Folder 47, Folder 48 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 52
Gillet, M. E. Mayor of Tampa, Florida Roll II Folder 14
Giménez, Jose Roll IV Folder 30
Glendale, Battle of Roll I Folder 1 Roll VI Folder 50, Folder 54, Folder 57